{
        "Geography": [
            {
                "question": "What is the capital of France?",
                "options": ["Paris", "London", "Rome", "Berlin"],
                "answer": "Paris"
            },
            {
                "question": "Mount Everest is located in which country?",
                "options": ["India", "Bhutan", "Nepal", "China"],
                "answer": "Nepal"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which river is the longest in the world?",
                "options": ["Amazon River", "Yangtze River", "Mississippi River", "Nile River"],
                "answer": "Nile River"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of the following countries is the smallest by area?",
                "options": ["Vatican City", "Monaco", "Luxembourg", "Andorra"],
                "answer": "Vatican City"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the largest desert in the world?",
                "options": ["Sahara Desert", "Arabian Desert", "Gobi Desert", "Antarctic Desert"],
                "answer": "Antarctic Desert"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which is the smallest continent by land area?",
                "options": ["Europe", "Australia", "Antarctica", "South America"],
                "answer": "Australia"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which country has the most number of islands?",
                "options": ["Finland", "Norway", "Canada", "Sweden"],
                "answer": "Sweden"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the capital of Australia?",
                "options": ["Sydney", "Melbourne", "Brisbane", "Canberra"],
                "answer": "Canberra"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which country is the world's highest waterfall, Angel Falls, located?",
                "options": ["USA", "Brazil", "Venezuela", "Argentina"],
                "answer": "Venezuela"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which is the largest ocean on Earth?",
                "options": ["Atlantic Ocean", "Indian Ocean", "Pacific Ocean", "Arctic Ocean"],
                "answer": "Pacific Ocean"
            }
        ],
        "History": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the document known as the 95 Theses?",
                "options": ["Martin Luther", "John Calvin", "Henry VIII", "Pope Leo X"],
                "answer": "Martin Luther"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year did World War I begin?",
                "options": ["1905", "1914", "1918", "1921"],
                "answer": "1914"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who was the first president of the United States?",
                "options": ["Abraham Lincoln", "George Washington", "Thomas Jefferson", "John Adams"],
                "answer": "George Washington"
            },
            {
                "question": "What city was the first capital of the Kingdom of Italy after its unification?",
                "options": ["Venice", "Rome", "Turin", "Florence"],
                "answer": "Turin"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which famous leader was assassinated on the Ides of March?",
                "options": ["Cleopatra", "Julius Caesar", "Augustus Caesar", "Spartacus"],
                "answer": "Julius Caesar"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which document, signed in 1215, was England's first constitution?",
                "options": ["The English Bill of Rights", "The Magna Carta", "The Petition of Right", "The Habeas Corpus Act"],
                "answer": "The Magna Carta"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who was the longest reigning British monarch as of 2021?",
                "options": ["Queen Elizabeth I", "Queen Elizabeth II", "Queen Victoria", "King George III"],
                "answer": "Queen Elizabeth II"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which city was the Titanic built?",
                "options": ["London", "Belfast", "Glasgow", "Liverpool"],
                "answer": "Belfast"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which civilization built the Machu Picchu complex in Peru?",
                "options": ["Maya", "Aztec", "Inca", "Olmec"],
                "answer": "Inca"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which historical event took place in the Bay of Pigs?",
                "options": ["Spanish-American War", "Cuban Missile Crisis", "Bay of Pigs Invasion", "Suez Crisis"],
                "answer": "Bay of Pigs Invasion"
            }
        ],
        "Math": [
            {
                "question": "What is the square root of 144?",
                "options": ["12", "14", "16", "18"],
                "answer": "12"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the derivative of x^2?",
                "options": ["x^2", "2x", "x", "2x^2"],
                "answer": "2x"
            },
            {
                "question": "How many sides does a decagon have?",
                "options": ["8", "10", "12", "14"],
                "answer": "10"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the value of Pi up to three decimal places?",
                "options": ["3.141", "3.123", "3.111", "3.131"],
                "answer": "3.141"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the sum of angles in a triangle (in degrees)?",
                "options": ["90", "180", "270", "360"],
                "answer": "180"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the binary equivalent of the decimal number 10?",
                "options": ["110", "101", "1001", "1010"],
                "answer": "1010"
            },
            {
                "question": "What does the 'Pythagorean Theorem' state for a right triangle?",
                "options": ["a^2 + b^2 = c^2", "a^2 - b^2 = c^2", "a^2 + b^2 > c^2", "a^2 + b^2 < c^2"],
                "answer": "a^2 + b^2 = c^2"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you calculate the area of a circle?",
                "options": ["pi*r^2", "2*pi*r", "pi*r", "2*pi*r^2"],
                "answer": "pi*r^2"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the next number in the series: 2, 4, 8, 16, ...?",
                "options": ["18", "20", "32", "30"],
                "answer": "32"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is 7^0?",
                "options": ["0", "1", "7", "undefined"],
                "answer": "1"
            }
        ],
        "Physics": [
            {
                "question": "What is the SI unit of force?",
                "options": ["Newton", "Watt", "Joule", "Pascal"],
                "answer": "Newton"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of the following is an example of a vector quantity?",
                "options": ["Mass", "Temperature", "Speed", "Displacement"],
                "answer": "Displacement"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the formula for calculating velocity?",
                "options": ["v = d/t", "v = F/m", "v = m*a", "v = P/t"],
                "answer": "v = d/t"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the law of conservation of energy?",
                "options": ["Energy can neither be created nor destroyed", "Energy can be created but not destroyed", "Energy can be destroyed but not created", "Energy is constant"],
                "answer": "Energy can neither be created nor destroyed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the formula for calculating work?",
                "options": ["W = F*d", "W = m*g", "W = P/t", "W = V/I"],
                "answer": "W = F*d"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of the following is an example of an insulator?",
                "options": ["Copper", "Aluminum", "Wood", "Silver"],
                "answer": "Wood"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the SI unit of electric current?",
                "options": ["Volt", "Ampere", "Coulomb", "Ohm"],
                "answer": "Ampere"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which law states that the pressure of a gas is inversely proportional to its volume at constant temperature?",
                "options": ["Boyle's Law", "Charles's Law", "Gay-Lussac's Law", "Avogadro's Law"],
                "answer": "Boyle's Law"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the formula for calculating power?",
                "options": ["P = F*d", "P = m*a", "P = W/t", "P = V/I"],
                "answer": "P = W/t"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the acceleration due to gravity on Earth?",
                "options": ["9.8 m/s^2", "6.7 m/s^2", "4.9 m/s^2", "12.5 m/s^2"],
                "answer": "9.8 m/s^2"
            }
        ],
        "Anatomy": [
            {
                "question": "Which organ is responsible for pumping blood throughout the body?",
                "options": ["Liver", "Lungs", "Heart", "Kidneys"],
                "answer": "Heart"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the largest organ in the human body?",
                "options": ["Liver", "Skin", "Lungs", "Brain"],
                "answer": "Skin"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which bone protects the brain?",
                "options": ["Skull", "Spine", "Ribcage", "Femur"],
                "answer": "Skull"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which system is responsible for delivering oxygen to the body and removing carbon dioxide?",
                "options": ["Nervous system", "Endocrine system", "Respiratory system", "Digestive system"],
                "answer": "Respiratory system"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which part of the eye is responsible for controlling the amount of light entering the eye?",
                "options": ["Iris", "Cornea", "Retina", "Lens"],
                "answer": "Iris"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which muscle is responsible for breathing?",
                "options": ["Biceps", "Quadriceps", "Diaphragm", "Pectoralis"],
                "answer": "Diaphragm"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which organ is responsible for filtering waste from the blood and producing urine?",
                "options": ["Liver", "Pancreas", "Spleen", "Kidneys"],
                "answer": "Kidneys"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the largest part of the human brain?",
                "options": ["Cerebrum", "Cerebellum", "Medulla oblongata", "Hypothalamus"],
                "answer": "Cerebrum"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which system is responsible for producing and transmitting electrical signals in the body?",
                "options": ["Muscular system", "Circulatory system", "Nervous system", "Skeletal system"],
                "answer": "Nervous system"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which part of the digestive system is responsible for absorbing nutrients from food?",
                "options": ["Stomach", "Large intestine", "Small intestine", "Esophagus"],
                "answer": "Small intestine"
            }
        ],
        "Computer Games": [
            {
                "question": "Which game features a world populated by blocks and allows players to build and explore?",
                "options": ["Minecraft", "Fortnite", "League of Legends", "Call of Duty"],
                "answer": "Minecraft"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game features a battle royale mode where 100 players fight to be the last one standing?",
                "options": ["Fortnite", "Apex Legends", "PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds", "Fall Guys"],
                "answer": "Fortnite"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game is set in the fantasy world of Azeroth and allows players to create and control characters in a virtual world?",
                "options": ["World of Warcraft", "The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim", "Final Fantasy XIV", "Guild Wars 2"],
                "answer": "World of Warcraft"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game series features an ongoing battle between terrorists and counter-terrorists?",
                "options": ["Counter-Strike", "Rainbow Six Siege", "Call of Duty", "Battlefield"],
                "answer": "Counter-Strike"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game features a group of colorful, jelly-like characters that compete in various challenges?",
                "options": ["Fall Guys", "Among Us", "Overcooked", "Rocket League"],
                "answer": "Fall Guys"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game series features a futuristic, first-person shooter gameplay with advanced weapons and vehicles?",
                "options": ["Halo", "Destiny", "Titanfall", "Borderlands"],
                "answer": "Halo"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game features a virtual world where players can design and interact with their own virtual avatars?",
                "options": ["The Sims", "Second Life", "Animal Crossing", "Sims City"],
                "answer": "Second Life"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game series is known for its open-world exploration, quests, and role-playing elements?",
                "options": ["The Legend of Zelda", "Assassin's Creed", "GTA", "Final Fantasy"],
                "answer": "The Legend of Zelda"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game series is based on the popular book and TV series, allowing players to embark on epic adventures in a fantasy realm?",
                "options": ["The Witcher", "Game of Thrones", "Lord of the Rings", "Elder Scrolls"],
                "answer": "The Witcher"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which game features a futuristic sport where players control rocket-powered cars to score goals?",
                "options": ["Rocket League", "FIFA", "NBA 2K", "NFL Madden"],
                "answer": "Rocket League"
            }
        ],
        "FRIENDS": [
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Ross and Monica's sister?",
                "options": ["Phoebe", "Rachel", "Joey", "Emily"],
                "answer": "Phoebe"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which character famously said 'How you doin?'",
                "options": ["Chandler", "Ross", "Joey", "Monica"],
                "answer": "Joey"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Chandler's annoying roommate before Joey?",
                "options": ["Eddie", "Gunther", "Mike", "Richard"],
                "answer": "Eddie"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Ross and Monica's pet dog?",
                "options": ["Chick", "Duck", "Moo", "Whiskers"],
                "answer": "Chick"
            },
            {
                "question": "What song is Phoebe best known for?",
                "options": ["Smelly Cat", "I'll Be There for You", "Wonderwall", "My Generation"],
                "answer": "Smelly Cat"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which character had a third nipple?",
                "options": ["Ross", "Joey", "Chandler", "Phoebe"],
                "answer": "Chandler"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Ross and Monica's parents?",
                "options": ["Jack and Judy", "Frank and Alice", "Frank and Phoebe", "Richard and Emily"],
                "answer": "Jack and Judy"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Rachel's sister?",
                "options": ["Phoebe", "Monica", "Amy", "Emily"],
                "answer": "Amy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which character worked as a paleontologist?",
                "options": ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Rachel"],
                "answer": "Ross"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin?",
                "options": ["Hugsy", "Waddle", "Mr. Penguin", "Penny"],
                "answer": "Hugsy"
            }
        ],
        "FORTNITE": [
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Floss", "Orange Justice", "The Robot", "Take the L"],
                "answer": "Floss"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which season introduced the map update that included Tilted Towers?",
                "options": ["Season 1", "Season 2", "Season 3", "Season 4"],
                "answer": "Season 3"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which location in Fortnite is a giant wooden llama?",
                "options": ["Pleasant Park", "Retail Row", "Lonely Lodge", "Junk Junction"],
                "answer": "Junk Junction"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the main currency used in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["V-Bucks", "Battle Stars", "Gold Bars", "Experience Points"],
                "answer": "V-Bucks"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which weapon was temporarily removed from Fortnite due to balancing issues?",
                "options": ["Rocket Launcher", "Shotgun", "Scoped Assault Rifle", "Infinity Blade"],
                "answer": "Infinity Blade"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which event in Fortnite temporarily caused the map to be covered in snow?",
                "options": ["Butterfly Event", "Ice Storm Event", "Cube Event", "The End Event"],
                "answer": "Ice Storm Event"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the island in the middle of Loot Lake?",
                "options": ["Dragon's Roost", "Turtle Island", "Viking Outpost", "Dusty Depot"],
                "answer": "Turtle Island"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite game mode features teams of 20 players battling it out?",
                "options": ["Solo", "Duo", "Squad", "Team Rumble"],
                "answer": "Team Rumble"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the large purple cube that appeared in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Midas", "Dark Voyager", "Thanos", "Kevin the Cube"],
                "answer": "Kevin the Cube"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of mythic weapons?",
                "options": ["Season 6", "Season 7", "Season 8", "Season 9"],
                "answer": "Season 9"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of building?",
                "options": ["Season 1", "Season 2", "Season 3", "Season 4"],
                "answer": "Season 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the main playable character in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Jonesy", "Ramirez", "Sarah", "Harper"],
                "answer": "Jonesy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the Battle Pass?",
                "options": ["Season 1", "Season 2", "Season 3", "Season 4"],
                "answer": "Season 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular weapon that shoots rockets in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Rocket Launcher", "Grenade Launcher", "Bazooka", "RPG"],
                "answer": "Rocket Launcher"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which location in Fortnite is a large desert biome?",
                "options": ["Paradise Palms", "Salty Springs", "Lazy Links", "Loot Lake"],
                "answer": "Paradise Palms"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the game mode in Fortnite where players compete to be the last one standing?",
                "options": ["Battle Royale", "Save the World", "Creative", "Team Rumble"],
                "answer": "Battle Royale"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of vehicles?",
                "options": ["Season 3", "Season 4", "Season 5", "Season 6"],
                "answer": "Season 3"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the location in Fortnite where players can access vending machines to trade materials for weapons?",
                "options": ["Vending Valley", "Trade Town", "Item Exchange", "Vending Machine City"],
                "answer": "Vending Machine City"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of Creative mode?",
                "options": ["Season 7", "Season 8", "Season 9", "Season 10"],
                "answer": "Season 7"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the rarest type of item in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Mythic", "Legendary", "Epic", "Rare"],
                "answer": "Mythic"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of swimming and underwater gameplay?",
                "options": ["Season 2", "Season 3", "Season 4", "Season 5"],
                "answer": "Season 3"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that originated from the TV show 'Scrubs'?",
                "options": ["Scrubs Dance", "Best Friends Dance", "Take the L", "Fresh Dance"],
                "answer": "Take the L"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of fishing and fishing spots?",
                "options": ["Season 7", "Season 8", "Season 9", "Season 10"],
                "answer": "Season 9"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the main antagonist in Fortnite's Save the World mode?",
                "options": ["The Storm King", "The Cube", "The Ice King", "The Dark Voyager"],
                "answer": "The Storm King"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of Chapter 2?",
                "options": ["Season 10", "Season 11", "Season 12", "Season 13"],
                "answer": "Season 11"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the futuristic city location in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Neo Tilted", "Mega City", "Techno Town", "Futuristic Frenzy"],
                "answer": "Neo Tilted"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Mandalorian and Baby Yoda as crossover characters?",
                "options": ["Season 4", "Season 5", "Season 6", "Season 7"],
                "answer": "Season 5"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the high-tech vehicle in Fortnite that can transform into a ball for fast mobility?",
                "options": ["Quadcrasher", "Driftboard", "Baller", "Grappler"],
                "answer": "Baller"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of Mythic Goldfish, an extremely rare and powerful throwable item?",
                "options": ["Season 8", "Season 9", "Season X", "Chapter 2 Season 1"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 1"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the location in Fortnite where players can access upgrade benches to enhance their weapons?",
                "options": ["Upgrade Station", "Enhancement Depot", "Weapon Workshop", "Power-Up Center"],
                "answer": "Upgrade Station"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of Bounty Hunters and NPCs that can be hired to aid players?",
                "options": ["Season 5", "Season 6", "Season 7", "Season 8"],
                "answer": "Season 5"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the large snowy mountain in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Frosty Peaks", "Snowy Summit", "Mount Chill", "Polar Peak"],
                "answer": "Polar Peak"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Primal and Mechanical weapon variants?",
                "options": ["Season 5", "Season 6", "Season 7", "Season 8"],
                "answer": "Season 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that features a character swinging their arms and hips?",
                "options": ["Hype", "Dance Moves", "Electro Shuffle", "Groove Jam"],
                "answer": "Electro Shuffle"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Spire and the Guardians?",
                "options": ["Season 6", "Season 7", "Season 8", "Season 9"],
                "answer": "Season 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the island in Fortnite where players spawn at the beginning of a match?",
                "options": ["Battle Island", "Starting Point", "Spawn Island", "Battle Bus"],
                "answer": "Spawn Island"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of Exotic Weapons, special weapons that can only be obtained by purchasing them from specific NPCs?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 2", "Chapter 2 Season 3", "Chapter 2 Season 4", "Chapter 2 Season 5"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 5"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that features a character swinging their arms and legs in a random pattern?",
                "options": ["Dab", "Wiggle", "Flapper", "Dance Therapy"],
                "answer": "Flapper"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Zero Point and the Nexus War?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 2", "Chapter 2 Season 3", "Chapter 2 Season 4", "Chapter 2 Season 5"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 4"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the large volcano location in Fortnite?",
                "options": ["Volcanic Valley", "Lava Lake", "Molten Mountain", "Pressure Plant"],
                "answer": "Pressure Plant"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Seven and the Alien Invasion storyline?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 3", "Chapter 2 Season 4", "Chapter 2 Season 5", "Chapter 2 Season 6"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that features a character doing a fast-paced dance routine?",
                "options": ["Renegade", "Slick", "Fast Feet", "Pump It Up"],
                "answer": "Renegade"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Sideways and the Shadow Stones?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 5", "Chapter 2 Season 6", "Chapter 2 Season 7", "Chapter 2 Season 8"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 7"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the location in Fortnite where players can find a large spaceship and encounter alien creatures?",
                "options": ["Extraterrestrial Encampment", "Cosmic Compound", "UFO Landing Zone", "Holly Hedges"],
                "answer": "Cosmic Compound"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Foundation and the Primal Hunters storyline?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 6", "Chapter 2 Season 7", "Chapter 2 Season 8", "Chapter 2 Season 9"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 7"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that features a character doing a funny and exaggerated dance routine?",
                "options": ["Best Mates", "Breakin'", "Make It Rain", "Pop Lock"],
                "answer": "Best Mates"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Cube Monsters and the Cube Event?",
                "options": ["Season 5", "Season 6", "Season 7", "Season 8"],
                "answer": "Season 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the location in Fortnite where players can find a floating island that moves around the map?",
                "options": ["Skyland", "Floating Fortress", "Airborne Atoll", "Levitating Island"],
                "answer": "Levitating Island"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of The Foundation and the Seven?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 6", "Chapter 2 Season 7", "Chapter 2 Season 8", "Chapter 2 Season 9"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that features a character pretending to ride an invisible horse?",
                "options": ["Ride the Pony", "Giddy-Up", "The Worm", "Rambunctious"],
                "answer": "Giddy-Up"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Mothership and the Alien Invasion storyline?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 7", "Chapter 2 Season 8", "Chapter 2 Season 9", "Chapter 2 Season 10"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 7"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the location in Fortnite where players can find a futuristic city with hovercars and advanced technology?",
                "options": ["Techno Town", "Sky City", "Futuristic Frenzy", "Neo Tilted"],
                "answer": "Neo Tilted"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Foundation and the Spire Guardians storyline?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 6", "Chapter 2 Season 7", "Chapter 2 Season 8", "Chapter 2 Season 9"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that features a character doing a smooth and rhythmic dance routine?",
                "options": ["Smooth Moves", "Flow", "Jubilation", "True Heart"],
                "answer": "Smooth Moves"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Sideways and the Cube Invasion storyline?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 5", "Chapter 2 Season 6", "Chapter 2 Season 7", "Chapter 2 Season 8"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 8"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the location in Fortnite where players can find a large amusement park with rides and attractions?",
                "options": ["Funland", "Pleasant Park", "Carnival Kingdom", "Weird World"],
                "answer": "Carnival Kingdom"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Fortnite season introduced the concept of the Foundation and the Cube War storyline?",
                "options": ["Chapter 2 Season 6", "Chapter 2 Season 7", "Chapter 2 Season 8", "Chapter 2 Season 9"],
                "answer": "Chapter 2 Season 8"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the popular dance emote that features a character doing a silly and playful dance routine?",
                "options": ["Groove Jam", "Pop Lock", "Boneless", "Rambunctious"],
                "answer": "Groove Jam"
            }
        ],
        "Billie Eilish": [
            {
                "question": "What is Billie Eilish's full name?",
                "options": ["Billie Marie Eilish", "Billie Eilish O'Connell", "Billie Rose Eilish", "Billie Elizabeth Baird"],
                "answer": "Billie Eilish O'Connell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of the following songs is NOT by Billie Eilish?",
                "options": ["Bad Guy", "Ocean Eyes", "Lovely", "Royals"],
                "answer": "Royals"
            },
            {
                "question": "At what age did Billie Eilish release her debut single 'Ocean Eyes'?",
                "options": ["14", "15", "16", "17"],
                "answer": "14"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song won Record of the Year at the 2020 Grammy Awards?",
                "options": ["Bad Guy", "Everything I Wanted", "When the Party's Over", "No Time to Die"],
                "answer": "Bad Guy"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year did Billie Eilish release her debut studio album 'When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?'?",
                "options": ["2017", "2018", "2019", "2020"],
                "answer": "2019"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which artist collaborated with Billie Eilish on the song 'Lovely'?",
                "options": ["Khalid", "Justin Bieber", "Phoebe Bridgers", "Finneas"],
                "answer": "Khalid"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's James Bond theme song released in 2020?",
                "options": ["No Time to Die", "Skyfall", "The Writing's on the Wall", "GoldenEye"],
                "answer": "No Time to Die"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which song by Billie Eilish includes the lyrics 'I'm the bad guy, duh'?",
                "options": ["Bury a Friend", "When the Party's Over", "Bad Guy", "My Future"],
                "answer": "Bad Guy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish album features the songs 'Therefore I Am' and 'Your Power'?",
                "options": ["Happier Than Ever", "When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?", "Don't Smile at Me", "No Time to Die"],
                "answer": "Happier Than Ever"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which country is Billie Eilish from?",
                "options": ["United States", "United Kingdom", "Canada", "Australia"],
                "answer": "United States"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song features the lyrics 'I'm that bad type, make your mama sad type'?",
                "options": ["Bad Guy", "When the Party's Over", "Bury a Friend", "Everything I Wanted"],
                "answer": "Bad Guy"
            },
            {
                "question": "What was the first song Billie Eilish recorded and released on SoundCloud?",
                "options": ["Ocean Eyes", "Bellyache", "Lovely", "Six Feet Under"],
                "answer": "Ocean Eyes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which artist did Billie Eilish collaborate with on the song 'My Future'?",
                "options": ["Finneas", "Khalid", "Phoebe Bridgers", "James Blake"],
                "answer": "Finneas"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'I can't seem to focus, and you don't seem to notice'?",
                "options": ["Ilomilo", "Xanny", "Everything I Wanted", "Listen Before I Go"],
                "answer": "Ilomilo"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Billie Eilish's debut EP released in 2017?",
                "options": ["Don't Smile at Me", "When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?", "Happier Than Ever", "Lovely"],
                "answer": "Don't Smile at Me"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song features the lyrics 'Please don't try to kiss me on the sidewalk'?",
                "options": ["Hostage", "My Strange Addiction", "Bellyache", "Watch"],
                "answer": "Hostage"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's documentary film released in 2021?",
                "options": ["The World's a Little Blurry", "Billie Eilish: The Story Behind", "Inside Billie's World", "Eilish: A Music Journey"],
                "answer": "The World's a Little Blurry"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'Call me friend but keep me closer'?",
                "options": ["Copycat", "When I Was Older", "Xanny", "Everything I Wanted"],
                "answer": "Copycat"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year did Billie Eilish win all four major Grammy Awards (Record of the Year, Album of the Year, Song of the Year, and Best New Artist)?",
                "options": ["2019", "2020", "2021", "2022"],
                "answer": "2020"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's collaboration with Rosalía released in 2021?",
                "options": ["Lo Vas a Olvidar", "Lost Cause", "My Future", "Therefore I Am"],
                "answer": "Lo Vas a Olvidar"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which song by Billie Eilish was used as the theme song for the Netflix series '13 Reasons Why'?",
                "options": ["Lovely", "Bored", "Six Feet Under", "Hostage"],
                "answer": "Lovely"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'So you're a tough guy, like it really rough guy'?",
                "options": ["Bury a Friend", "You Should See Me in a Crown", "When the Party's Over", "My Strange Addiction"],
                "answer": "You Should See Me in a Crown"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Billie Eilish's debut studio album?",
                "options": ["When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?", "Happier Than Ever", "Don't Smile at Me", "Billie Eilish"],
                "answer": "When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'Quiet when I'm coming home and I'm on my own'?",
                "options": ["Bellyache", "Listen Before I Go", "Everything I Wanted", "I Love You"],
                "answer": "Everything I Wanted"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's collaboration with Khalid?",
                "options": ["Lovely", "Bad Guy", "When the Party's Over", "No Time to Die"],
                "answer": "Lovely"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'I'm in their secondhand smoke, still just drinking canned coke'?",
                "options": ["Watch", "Bellyache", "Ilomilo", "My Strange Addiction"],
                "answer": "My Strange Addiction"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the song Billie Eilish released for the James Bond film 'No Time to Die'?",
                "options": ["No Time to Die", "Bond Girl", "Dangerous Woman", "Spy in the Shadows"],
                "answer": "No Time to Die"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'I'll sit and watch your car burn with the fire that you started in me'?",
                "options": ["Watch", "Bellyache", "Listen Before I Go", "I Love You"],
                "answer": "Watch"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's song released for the Apple TV+ film 'Billie Eilish: The World's a Little Blurry'?",
                "options": ["Therefore I Am", "No Time to Die", "Everything I Wanted", "When the Party's Over"],
                "answer": "Therefore I Am"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'Don't you know too much already? I'll only hurt you if you let me'?",
                "options": ["Xanny", "My Strange Addiction", "Bury a Friend", "Listen Before I Go"],
                "answer": "Bury a Friend"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song features the lyrics 'You can't replace me, cannot unsee me'?",
                "options": ["Ilomilo", "Xanny", "Bad Guy", "Everything I Wanted"],
                "answer": "Ilomilo"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's collaboration with Justin Bieber?",
                "options": ["Bad Guy", "Lovely", "No Time to Die", "I Don't Care"],
                "answer": "Bad Guy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which song by Billie Eilish includes the lyrics 'I'm in the secondhand smoke, still just drinking canned Coke'?",
                "options": ["Watch", "Bellyache", "Copycat", "Hostage"],
                "answer": "Watch"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Billie Eilish's brother who often collaborates with her?",
                "options": ["Finneas", "Oliver", "Noah", "Ethan"],
                "answer": "Finneas"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'You say you're sorry, but it's too late now'?",
                "options": ["When the Party's Over", "Ocean Eyes", "Bury a Friend", "My Future"],
                "answer": "When the Party's Over"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's song released for the Netflix series 'To All the Boys: P.S. I Still Love You'?",
                "options": ["Everything I Wanted", "No Time to Die", "Lovely", "Six Feet Under"],
                "answer": "Everything I Wanted"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'If teardrops could be bottled, there'd be swimming pools filled by models'?",
                "options": ["Ocean Eyes", "Bellyache", "Lovely", "My Strange Addiction"],
                "answer": "My Strange Addiction"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's song released for the Apple TV+ film 'Billie Eilish: The World's a Little Blurry'?",
                "options": ["Everything I Wanted", "When the Party's Over", "Therefore I Am", "No Time to Die"],
                "answer": "Therefore I Am"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'I'm the bad type, make your mama sad type'?",
                "options": ["Bad Guy", "My Future", "You Should See Me in a Crown", "Lovely"],
                "answer": "Bad Guy"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's song released for the HBO series 'Euphoria'?",
                "options": ["Bury a Friend", "Hostage", "Lovely", "Wish You Were Gay"],
                "answer": "Bury a Friend"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'Wake up, you need to make money'?",
                "options": ["8", "Bellyache", "Copycat", "Idontwannabeyouanymore"],
                "answer": "8"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Billie Eilish's debut EP?",
                "options": ["Don't Smile at Me", "When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?", "Happier Than Ever", "Billie Eilish"],
                "answer": "Don't Smile at Me"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'You don't need to save me'?",
                "options": ["No Time to Die", "Everything I Wanted", "My Future", "Lovely"],
                "answer": "My Future"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's song released for the film 'The Turning'?",
                "options": ["Therefore I Am", "When the Party's Over", "Bellyache", "No Time to Die"],
                "answer": "No Time to Die"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'You better run from me'?",
                "options": ["You Should See Me in a Crown", "Copycat", "Bad Guy", "When the Party's Over"],
                "answer": "You Should See Me in a Crown"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Billie Eilish's official fanbase?",
                "options": ["Avocados", "Eilishers", "Billie's Army", "Bloomers"],
                "answer": "Avocados"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which song by Billie Eilish includes the lyrics 'So you're a tough guy, like it really rough guy'?",
                "options": ["Bury a Friend", "You Should See Me in a Crown", "When the Party's Over", "My Strange Addiction"],
                "answer": "You Should See Me in a Crown"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Billie Eilish's debut studio album?",
                "options": ["When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?", "Happier Than Ever", "Don't Smile at Me", "Billie Eilish"],
                "answer": "When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'Quiet when I'm coming home and I'm on my own'?",
                "options": ["Bellyache", "Listen Before I Go", "Everything I Wanted", "I Love You"],
                "answer": "Everything I Wanted"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the title of Billie Eilish's collaboration with Khalid?",
                "options": ["Lovely", "Bad Guy", "When the Party's Over", "No Time to Die"],
                "answer": "Lovely"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Billie Eilish song includes the lyrics 'I'm in their secondhand smoke, still just drinking canned coke'?",
                "options": ["Watch", "Bellyache", "Ilomilo", "My Strange Addiction"],
                "answer": "My Strange Addiction"
            }
        ],
        "Marvel": [
            {
                "question": "Who is the strongest Avenger?",
                "options": ["Iron Man", "Thor", "Hulk", "Captain America"],
                "answer": "Hulk"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the real name of the superhero Iron Man?",
                "options": ["Steve Rogers", "Bruce Wayne", "Tony Stark", "Peter Parker"],
                "answer": "Tony Stark"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Thor's enchanted hammer?",
                "options": ["Stormbreaker", "Mjolnir", "Gungnir", "Aegis"],
                "answer": "Mjolnir"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the main villain in the Avengers movie?",
                "options": ["Loki", "Thanos", "Red Skull", "Ultron"],
                "answer": "Loki"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of Captain America's shield?",
                "options": ["Star-Spangled Shield", "Patriot Shield", "Freedom Shield", "Vibranium Shield"],
                "answer": "Vibranium Shield"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Marvel character is known for saying 'I am Groot'?",
                "options": ["Rocket Raccoon", "Drax the Destroyer", "Groot", "Gamora"],
                "answer": "Groot"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the leader of the X-Men?",
                "options": ["Wolverine", "Professor X", "Cyclops", "Magneto"],
                "answer": "Professor X"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which Infinity Stone gives the power of time manipulation?",
                "options": ["Space Stone", "Mind Stone", "Reality Stone", "Time Stone"],
                "answer": "Time Stone"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the alter ego of the superhero Black Widow?",
                "options": ["Natasha Romanoff", "Wanda Maximoff", "Carol Danvers", "Hope Van Dyne"],
                "answer": "Natasha Romanoff"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the planet where the Guardians of the Galaxy first meet?",
                "options": ["Xandar", "Sakaar", "Knowhere", "Ego"],
                "answer": "Knowhere"
            }
        ]
}